RAFAEL PELLE

RONT-END DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I'm a reliable front-end developer with five years of experience with React. I like to mentor less experience developers, and i think the best solutions to problems are the simple ones.

Florianópolis, Brasil



✓ rafapelle@gmail.com



https://rafaelpelle.tech/en



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/rafa el-pelle-23429317a/

SKILLS

- React
- Next.js
- TypeScript
- Redux
- React Query
- Automated testing
- Wireframe creation
- Collaboration

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Universidade Federal de Santa Catarina (UFSC)

2013 - 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

AMARO (SENIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER)

Sep 2021 - Mar 2023

Working at AMARO I was responsible for maintaining features and create new ones on the company's e-commerce. It was my first time working with design system, micro front-ends, web vitals, data analytics and SEO. Had daily experience with error logging and monitoring. Also had the opportunity to collaborate in a large team of front-end developers with pair programming, code review and mentoring less experience developers. (TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, React Query, SASS, Figma...)

SUPERO TECNOLOGIA (MID FRONT-END DEVELOPER) Oct 2019 - Sep 2021

At Supero software factory I've worked with multiple projects for different clients, maintaining legacy code and building projects from scratch. Usually working as the only front-end developer on the project, without code review, but delivering reliable features and fixes. (React, Redux, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Figma...)

GETMORE SERVIÇOS (JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER)

May 2018 - Oct 2019

It was my first internship and then full-time job. I had the opportunity to collaborate not only in software development, but in the business development too, because it was a startup without a well defined product. I was the only front-end developer at my squad and we created a white-label cashback platform from scratch to rent to multiple clients. It was rented to the next bank. I was mentored by a more experienced developer and I saw how important it is. That's why I like to help less experienced developers to improve their skills. (React, Redux, TypeScript, Material-UI, Figma...)